David



PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a software engineering student. I've worked on framework-based projects for the creation of progressive apps. During my studies, I earned Ciso R&S certificates. I have expertise organizing a tech support team by standardizing the requirements of businesses to reach the goals. I am a very appasionate person for the programing on the frontend side with framework as Angular and Next.js

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Cisco Certification CCNAv7: Switching, Routing, and Wireless
- · Cisco Certification CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks
- · Javascript Sololearn
- · CSS Sololearn

HOW TO CONTACT ME

- +57 (313) 814-7344
- xddavidxd2001@gmail.com
- https://github.com/DavidRedz10
- www.linkedin.com/in/david-rojas-e

PERSONAL REFERENCES

FERLEIN ROJAS QUIROGA

Phone 3214929033

JUAN JOSÉ PÉREZ

Phone 3112890065

KEVIN ANDRÉS ARDILA

Phone 3115894758

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

Manuela Beltran University- Current

• Ongoing engineer (tenth semester) with knowledge in the use of front-end and mobile technologies as well a networking knowledge.

High School

Elisa Borrero de Pastrana School / 2004-2017

 Certified by SENA as a Technician in Accounting for Financial Operations.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Lean Tech - Current

Helpdesk Specialist Aug 2022

Using JIRA, Zendesk, and MongoDB to monitor the issue resolution, feature requests, and enhancements of a U.S. logistics platform.

Adoptapp

Mobile app June 2020 - Ene 2021

Help in the UI design with responsibility for the design system, collaborate for main cross-platform application development using technologies such as AngularJS and CSS.

Ontop Inc.

Contractor Specialist Mar 2022 - May 2022

Onboard the customers to the Ontop payment experience as well as being a point of contact for inquiries in regard their contracts.

Sitel Group

Customer service associate Nov 2020 - Aug2022

Customer care representative for a digital wallet and mobile payment software in the US.